const questions = [
  {
    question: "1. How do you write 'Hello World' in an alert box?",
    choices: [
      "msg('Hello World')",
      "msgBox('Hello World');",
      "alertBox('Hello World');",
      "alert('Hello World');",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "2. Inside which HTML element do you put the JavaScript?",
    choices: ["<javascript>", "<link>", "<script", "<style>"],
    correctAnswer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "3. What is the correct location to insert a Javascript tag?",
    choices: [
      "The <head> section",
      "The <body> section",
      "The <style> section",
      "Both the <head> and <body> section will work",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "4. What is the correct syntax for referring to an external script called 'app.js'?",
    choices: [
      "<script href='app.js'>",
      "<script src='app.js'>",
      "<script link='app.js'>",
      "<script name='app.js'>",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "5. How do you call a function named'setInterval'?",
    choices: [
      "setInterval()",
      "call setInterval()",
      "call function setInterval()",
      "run setInterval()",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "6. How do you write an 'if' statement in javascript?",
    choices: ["if i = 5", "if i === 5", "if (i == 5)", "if i = 5 then"],
    correctAnswer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "7. What does CSS stand for?",
    choices: [
      "Cascading Style Sheet",
      "Computer Style Sheets",
      "Creative Style Sheets",
      "Condensed Style Sheets",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "8. Which is the correct CSS syntax?",
    choices: [
      "body:color=black;",
      "{body:color=black;}",
      "{body;color:black}",
      "body{color:black;}",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "9. How do you insert a comment in a CSS file?",
    choices: [
      "// this is a comment //",
      "// this is a comment",
      "/* this is a comment */",
      "'this is a comment",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "10. Which property is used to change the background color?",
    choices: ["background-color", "color", "bgColor", "set-background"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "11. Which property is used to change the text size?",
    choices: ["font-style", "text-style", "font-size", "text-size"],
    correctAnswer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "12. How do you select an element with an id of 'demo'?",
    choices: ["demo", "*demo", ".demo", "#demo"],
    correctAnswer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "13. What is the correct HTML element for the largest heading?",
    choices: ["<h1>", "<heading>", "<h6>", "<headXL>"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "14. How can you open a link in a new tab?",
    choices: [
      "<a href='url' new>",
      "<a href='url' target='new'>",
      "<a href='url' target='_blank'>",
      "<a href='url' newTarget>",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "15. Which HTML attribute specifies an alternate text for an image, if the image cannot be display?",
    choices: ["description=''", "alt=''", "src=''", "title=''"],
    correctAnswer: 1,
  },
];
